Today is the 4th day in Fukuoka!
I'm having too much fun!
What a surprise, we had 3 nights and 4 days in Fukuoka this time!
Actually, we're having a lot of fun!
Yes, that's right!
Free live concerts were held on Saturday and Sunday.
Yesterday, the second day was over.
The last day was with Haru.
Where are you going?
We're going to Itoshima.
Yay!
It's my first time to Itoshima.
It's my second time.
The first time was...
I don't remember when.
Oh, okay, that's enough then.
Lily and I even appealed to you.
I went there when I went there.
It was just, you know...
It was raining.
Oh, really?
Itoshima faces the ocean.
It's a beautiful place.
It was cloudy.
It's so sunny today.
Yes, it's a beautiful day.
It's a beautiful day.
We've narrowed down all the places we want to go today.
I've got it all planned out.
I'll leave the driving to Spring.
I'm off!
First, Totoro Forest.
Haru said she wanted to go there.
That Totoro scene looks familiar.
Yeah, yeah, we're going in.
You know, the first scene where they're chasing Totoro?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Like a tunnel.
Like a tunnel.
A big place.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Go to Totoro's forest.
Go for a walk.
There's a park or something.
And if you go a little off the beaten path...
What's the ocean?
I don't think so.
There's some kind of tiny sandy beach.
We could go there, too.
We'll decide where to have lunch.
There's some kind of fishing port around there.
There's a fishing port around there, so there should be lots of fish.
And seafood.
You've already eaten.
Yes, I did.
You've already conquered it.
Yes, I did... on the fourth day.
Yes.
But I want to eat at the port, where I can see the ocean.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
I want to eat.
Yeah. - Yeah.
And then...
After that...
Rokuro
I'll go to the mountain pass.
not bad
dangerous
History of Rokuro
At last
straddle the sword
Right.
Kyushu once
Once in Kyushu
And when I came last year...
Oi...
I went to Nagai and other places.
I was talking about how I wanted to do Rokuro
I was talking about doing ROKURO there, too.
I just didn't have time.
That's right.
The rokuro takes a lot of time.
I'll take about two hours, give or take.
I'll take about two hours.
It's up to you.
That's right.
With the wheelchair.
And, well, it would be nice if we could stop by a cafe or something.
That's about right.
Yes, sir.
Spend some time.
We'll have dinner at the airport.
That'll be fun.
What shall we eat?
I can't tell you how many times I've eaten in Fukuoka.
Almost ate.
It's like a long-established
Oyakodon-like place, right?
Yes, it's recommended by the locals.
Yeah...
What's this place like a shopping arcade?
It's like Fukuoka soup stock.
That's right.
That's what Yukirinu said.
Yes, like Fukuoka's soup stock.
A place where you can taste the city.
Tobi Ume?
It's in the new manager's office.
Near Parco, right?
I asked for a recommendation.
They said we might be the last in line.
We both went there, and there was a table open.
We were lucky.
I'm going to try it again.
That's right.
Lucky!
It was like a mission accomplished.
It always works out, doesn't it?
It's great, isn't it?
We always have a plan, and it's going to work today, too.
The other day in Oita...
It was great!
We went to Fukuoka the other day.
I said I wanted to go to the hot springs.
But it was too foggy.
It was so foggy that we had to go to Yee-haw in the fog.
It was a day trip rep.
We had lunch at a very high speed.
We took a bath at a very high speed.
It's a famous place.
We were only out there for about a half hour.
I can clear what I want to do.
I'm gonna go to the hot springs.
I have no regrets.
I mean, when we went to Karatsu...
It was perfect.
The girl I'm going to call?
She was great, right?
I'm sure it'll be perfect today too.
I'll call you next time I get to Itoshima.
We were already in Itoshima.
Lots of forest.
We're in the mountains.
We should be able to see the ocean soon.
It's on a little bit.
The map looks like it's already along the ocean.
The trees are pretty healthy.
Keep going straight and you'll get there.
Totoro Forest
One more kilometer and we'll be in Totoro Woods.
Hungry?
Not yet.
We've got a lot of walking to do.
It starts at 1:30, right?
We'll leave a little after 1:00.
We have two and a half hours.
We can walk around for a little over an hour.
Keya's Oto Park.
I need a snack to drink.
Nature's at her best in the morning.
Great.
I'm already hungry... in the center.
Yes, I've eaten.
I'll wait till the end.
Okay, we're ready.
Here we are.
I'll set it up for you.
Thank you.
Here we are.
It's so bright.
It's a really nice place.
It's not a really nice place.
What is it?
Wait...
It's like Spirited Away.
What's that?
The one in front of the tunnel.
This... this...
This one...
It would be great if there was a tunnel
Cars would stop, right?
In this case
I might have something good for you.
All right, all right. Let's go look at the map.
Let's go look at the map.
Let's go look at the map first.
We're looking for Totoro's Forest.
Totoro's
It's warm, but
The wind is properly cold
It's so nice!
Both of us are wearing sneakers today
Yes, we're ready to walk
They're ready to walk.
Are they getting ready?
Two days?
Two days.
Where's Mr. Totoro?
Wasn't he at the tip of something?
Wasn't it somewhere around here?
That means we have to walk this way.
It's already here?
Is that it?
It's okay!
You want to go?
That's it!
I thought you were going to take a little more of a walk.
I didn't expect you to come out so soon.
Totoro!
Wow, so much ocean!
The ocean!
Oh, it's so beautiful!
It's amazing!
Are we filming each other?
You don't have your Totoro badge?
Yeah!
I'll throw in a mini badge!
Oh!
Enjoy the Totoro Forest side with the Nao Camera!
Totoro!
Oh, my gosh!
That's amazing!
I wonder how far it goes?
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
Can you see it?
It's so good! It's so beautiful!
Looking good! It's so good!
So smart now.
Good, good, good.
Vertical.
It's so beautiful.
It's so close! It's so close!
I climbed up.
It's pretty good. Each step is good exercise.
I'm all alone now, so I'm making it all relevant.
Behind the top of Howl, there's an old lady going up the stairs.
What a pity!
I can definitely see that.
It's over here
Yes, yes, yes, yes
You're out of breath, though.
I thought it was just one big place that was too far away.
It's long.
It's gonna open up.
Isn't that the mystery tree? The telegraph stand.
Isn't this the mystery tree?
It's definitely this one.
This is it.
What do you think?
It's amazing.
Oh, my God.
Ocean view.
It's so beautiful.
Overlooking the ocean.
Oh, my God.
It's flying high!
Next notice
Going downhill, going downhill!
We're coming down!
Now, look at the sea
Oh, it's the ocean!
The sea water is so beautiful!
It's so clear!
Amazing!
It feels so good.
It feels so nice!
It's really more beautiful overseas!
Yeah, it's so beautiful!
We got lucky with the ocean.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, wow.
It's a rock.
It's got a tail.
It's in the ocean.
But it's scary.
Scary.
My hair.
Where is it?
Aah!
Oh, that's good.
I feel like I'm doing this more often than not.
It's so good!
Selfie's over.
You're so cute.
It's cute, but it's dangerous.
Okay, here we go.
I'm doing it this time, but take the picture with this.
Oh, my God.
Look at that.
Oh, my God!
That's really good.
That's great.
Good night. - Good night.
Good night.
Ta-da!
Wow, look at that.
Curry shild
Miso soup and
Good night
Onsen egg and steamed egg custard are also included!
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
I'm full!
Looks delicious!
I'm full.
I'm full
So full!
I also took some nori (seaweed).
Is there a sesame seed hole?
Yes.
Anma.
Stuffed with sesame seeds.
I'm going to eat it again.
I'm gonna have another one of these.
This one.
Delicious.
Delicious!
It's great!
I eat a lot!
Looking at the contents of the toy,
You can see what's inside the toy.
Goooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Wow!
It's taking shape!
If you look back at this a few times, it becomes a picture.
On your own.
Put some water on it again.
Make it slippery.
After holding down this wall
with your left hand.
pull it to the top panel with a goof.
Oh!
Oh, wow!
Give it a slow pinch.
It's clean.
You were slipping.
Now just hold it tight.
Are you okay?
I'm very okay.
It's done!
Choco! Choco!
I'll start with the meat.
Let's go with the meat.
A few more tray mugs
This is it!
This is the key
Let's go with the meat
I made something round and round!
Here's the plate I just made
This is Yawa-chan's plate
This is what it looks like.
You can do it!
That's great!
Don't let people run away.
Give them the ashes.
We're done.
I got a souvenir.
like a small wine glass.
I'm looking forward to concentrating and completing my ally!
Cute cafe
Cafe turn
Ah, here we are at Pannal!
Cute
Let's eat strawberries
It was a group phone.
You said that earlier.
I forgot about it.
How was Japan?
I'll have a fresh strawberry smoothie.
Whipped.
With ice cream.
Just the two of us.
Sweet.
You want to see sweet?
What's that?
The locals made it.
Sweet.
I'll wait for your order.
Looks delicious.
I had strawberry tea.
I had a sweet
Strawberry smoothie
Delicious!
Delicious
Jan-Jan.
Yummy?
I'm trying to remember what it was like to be a smarty-pants.
Peace to goo.
What did I do?
Fear.
Is that Peace?
I'm going to eat this one.
I'm going to eat it.
Yay!
Next time
With your phone.
You'll eat?
See you soon.
Watch again
See you again.
Go home.
Go home
I'm going home.
I almost missed the train.
I was so close.
I've had my fill. I'm going home.
I'm going home.
Return home